<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.sureassert.uc.feature"
      label="Sureassert UC Engine for Eclipse"
      version="2.0.0"
      provider-name="Sureassert">

   <description url="http://www.sureassert.com">
      Sureassert UC Engine for Eclipse
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright 2011 Nathan Dolan.  All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      Sureassert UC Engine for Eclipse - License
Definitions
&quot;You&quot; and &quot;your&quot; refers to the individual that wishes to use
the 
programs.
&quot;The copyright holder&quot; refers to Nathan Dolan.  
&quot;Programs&quot; refers to the Sureassert UC Engine for Eclipse.
&quot;Programs&quot; and &quot;Sureassert UC Engine&quot; does not include the 
Sureassert UC Annotation package (org.sureassert.uc.annotations)
which is downloaded and licensed separately.
&quot;License&quot; refers to your right to use the programs under the
terms of this agreement. 
This agreement is governed by the substantive and
procedural laws of the United Kingdom. You and the copyright
holder agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of, and
venue in, the courts of the United Kingdom in any dispute arising
out of or relating to this agreement. 
The copyright holder is willing to license the programs to you
only upon the condition that you accept all of the terms contained
in this agreement. If you are not willing to be bound by these
terms, do not download the software. 
License Rights
The copyright holder grants you a nonexclusive, non-transferable
limited license to use the programs for purposes of developing
your applications.
If you want to use the programs for any purpose
other than as expressly permitted under this agreement you must
contact the copyright holder to obtain the appropriate license.
Ownership and Restrictions
The copyright holder retains all ownership and intellectual property
rights in the programs. You may make a sufficient number of copies
of the programs for the licensed use by the individual licensed
user 
and one copy of the programs for backup purposes.
You may not: 
• use the programs for any purpose other than as provided above;
• distribute the programs; 
• charge your end users for use of the programs; 
• remove or modify any program markings or any notice of the
copyright holder’s proprietary rights; 
• use the programs to provide third party training on the content
and/or functionality of the programs unless with prior written
permission from the copyright holder (contact info@sureassert.com);
• assign this agreement or give the programs, program access
or an interest in the programs to any individual or entity; 
• cause or permit reverse engineering (unless required by law
for interoperability), disassembly or decompilation of the programs;
or,
• disclose results of any program benchmark tests without the
copyright holder’s prior consent.
• link software with the programs in any way other than the
intended use of executing the Sureassert UC Eclipse Builder on
software being developed by the user.
Disclaimer of Warranty and Exclusive Remedies
THE PROGRAMS ARE PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.
THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER FURTHER DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS
AND IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NONINFRINGEMENT.
IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT,
INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES
FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA OR DATA USE, INCURRED BY YOU
OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT OR TORT,
EVEN IF THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY
OF SUCH DAMAGES.
Technical Support
No technical support or updates will be provided to you for the
programs licensed under this agreement.
You may use the forums provided at www.sureassert.com to seek
technical support from the user community.  
End of Agreement
You may terminate this agreement by destroying all copies of
the programs. The copyright holder has the right to terminate
your right to use the programs if you fail to comply with any
of the terms of this agreement, in which case you shall destroy
all copies of the programs. 
Relationship Between the Parties
The relationship between you and the copyright holder is that
of licensee/licensor. Neither party will represent that it has
any authority to assume or create any obligation, express or
implied, on behalf of the other party, nor to represent the other
party as agent, employee, franchisee, or in any other capacity.
Nothing in this agreement shall be construed to limit either
party&apos;s right to independently develop or distribute software
that is functionally similar to the other party&apos;s products, so
long as proprietary information of the other party is not included
in such software. 
Entire Agreement
You agree that this agreement is the complete agreement for the
programs and licenses, and this agreement supersedes all prior
or contemporaneous agreements or representations. If any term
of this agreement is found to be invalid or unenforceable, the
remaining provisions will remain effective. 
Last updated: 23/05/2011
Should you have any questions concerning this License Agreement
please contact info@sureassert.com
   </license>

   <url>
      <discovery label="Sureassert home page" url="http://www.sureassert.com"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.pde.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.launching"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.ui"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.sureassert.uc"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.sureassert.uc.runtime"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.sureassert.uc.lib"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.sureassert.uc.runner"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.sureassert.uc.runner.init"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
